<?xml version="1.0"?>
<cues>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:00:00.00</start>
    <end>00:00:02.01</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: All right, go ahead.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:00:02.02</start>
    <end>00:00:14.01</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Hi, I’m Allison Foley, class of ’01 and originally from New Jersey, and then came here, and now I’m in Indiana and I don’t know where I’m going come August. Somewhere. But, y’know... Go ahead.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:00:14.02</start>
    <end>00:00:28.16</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I’m Tyler Bradbury, class of ’01 from California and I’m back in California via China, France, New York state, Nevada.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:00:28.17</start>
    <end>00:00:37.22</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Yeah, seriously. I like that we’re also looking at each other to confirm these things are true. Yeah, you’ve been all over the damn place. Well done.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:00:37.23</start>
    <end>00:00:38.19</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: And we were roommates.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:00:38.20</start>
    <end>00:00:39.11</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: We were roommates.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:00:39.12</start>
    <end>00:00:42.24</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: We met on the first day of our freshman year.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:00:42.25</start>
    <end>00:00:44.11</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Oh, wow.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:00:44.12</start>
    <end>00:00:44.17</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: On Main fourth.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:00:44.18</start>
    <end>00:00:47.12</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And then we immediately went out and bought that plant.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:00:47.13</start>
    <end>00:00:48.09</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Walter Hughes.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:00:48.10</start>
    <end>00:00:57.19</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Walter Hughes. And we would dance with him. This long, tendril-y plant. I'm impressed- I remember Walter.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:00:57.20</start>
    <end>00:00:59.29</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I remembered his name, not that we danced with him.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:01:00.00</start>
    <end>00:01:01.24</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Oh. I have pictures of you dancing with him.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:01:01.25</start>
    <end>00:01:02.04</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Really?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:01:02.05</start>
    <end>00:01:07.13</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Yes, ‘cause he had those… He. He had these long tendril-y things and you would waltz with him.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:01:07.14</start>
    <end>00:01:09.14</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Didn’t I take him home with me senior year?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:01:09.15</start>
    <end>00:01:09.28</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Yes.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:01:09.29</start>
    <end>00:01:17.06</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: And I snuck him into Cali– oh, I wonder if I should say this. [Laughing] I smuggled him past the border patrol in California.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:01:17.07</start>
    <end>00:01:23.07</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: No, we had little Walter juniors too ‘cause we took clippings and gave him around. I don’t know what happened to him, though.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:01:23.08</start>
    <end>00:01:25.23</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: He lived at my house for a while. I think my mom killed him.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:01:25.24</start>
    <end>00:01:28.10</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Oh, poor Walter.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:01:28.11</start>
    <end>00:01:30.25</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Well, do you have anything specific that you came in wanting to talk about?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:01:30.26</start>
    <end>00:01:43.08</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: No, I just really like oral history projects. So yeah I thought, “Oh, that'll be fun,” when other people said that they came in and did this so I was like, “Oh that'll be awesome. Let’s do that.”</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:01:43.09</start>
    <end>00:01:52.08</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Yeah, so I guess a couple questions to start out: How did you find out about Grinnell, and what made you decide to come to Grinnell?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:01:52.09</start>
    <end>00:02:30.23</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: What made me decide was, I, literally, I think I stepped onto campus and was like, “Yup, this is the one. Home.” But the way I found it- My mom was our college counselor and she was really big on me going to a school that I liked and I knew I didn’t want to go to a big school, and I was looking at Middlebury. She freaked out because it was all the way in Vermont instead of in California, and then we looked at a few schools in California and she kept saying things like, “Oh, I can come visit you on the weekend,” and so I was like, 'Okay. Compromise.' And I ended up in Iowa.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:02:30.24</start>
    <end>00:02:30.24</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Wow.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:02:30.25</start>
    <end>00:03:28.12</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Go figure. My mom and I used to watch Jeopardy all the time together, and we would battle, and I remember College Jeopardy, what, like 1994, ’95, a Grinnell woman won and we were like, “We’ve never heard of this school,” and immediately forgot about it until I started getting in the pamphlets and stuff. We were like, “Oh, that was that Grinnell lady. Oh, that was, oh, Jeopardy, yeah yeah yeah.” And then I was like, “Oh, it’s in Iowa? Mm.” and I threw it all away. I threw all of it away. I was like, 'I’m not moving to Iowa; I’m from New Jersey, and nah nah nah.' And then they sent this letter out and it, I wanna know who in the admissions office decided to do this ‘cause it was brilliant for those of us who are socially awkward. Where they sent this and like- “Maybe you lost our first mailing, or maybe you’re just so busy you didn’t have a chance to respond, but we really wanted to hear back,” and you know, I was like, [Gasps]. I felt so guilt-ridden that I wrote back. [Laughing]</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:03:28.13</start>
    <end>00:03:31.06</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: So basically Allison went to Grinnell from guilt.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:03:31.07</start>
    <end>00:03:45.03</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: But then they sent, like, the Exit 182 pamphlet and I was like, “Oh this is really fun.” It was all, like, the little drawings of the squirrels. Adam Wertzfeld’s drawings were in there. Oh, Adam Wertzfeld, he used to wear this scarf and swan around campus all the time. He was amazing.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:03:45.04</start>
    <end>00:03:48.21</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Was he part of the Scottish- “Freedom!”</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:03:48.22</start>
    <end>00:04:24.27</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: No… yes! Which mean- We saw him naked on a number of occasions. He'd come flash everybody. But, yeah, then, my mom and I flew out and it was a great visit except, and it had to have been a good visit because my marching band was supposed to be marching in Giants Stadium that weekend and I’ve never gotten to do that so, it’s a good thing I liked Grinnell. But yeah, we got here and we stepped onto campus and we watched someone slip and fall and a whole bunch of people came to help and then we went to dinner in Quad and everyone was so nice and Quad was so beautiful and it was so family-ish. I was like, 'Yeah, this is right.' So...</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:04:24.28</start>
    <end>00:04:31.07</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Was there a professor, student or staff member that particularly influenced you?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:04:31.08</start>
    <end>00:04:34.01</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Oh… just one?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:04:34.02</start>
    <end>00:04:35.28</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Or more.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:04:35.29</start>
    <end>00:05:04.04</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I- I don’t know. I mean, the faculty, yes, the faculty was great and they pushed you. I think at the time- now that I’m, maybe, faculty, I can kind of understand it a little bit more. But, I mean, you learn so much. You’re just a little sponge at that age. You just soak everything up and it’s all exciting and like 'Oh, they’re experts in things.' But yeah, I have a different perspective on it now. But all the other students- people were so cool, and everyone was so interesting.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:05:04.05</start>
    <end>00:05:07.16</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah, It was the students. I always thought it was everyone else.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:05:07.17</start>
    <end>00:05:15.20</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I think about that sometimes, like... We’re really interesting. It’d suck to go somewhere where people weren’t as interesting.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:05:15.21</start>
    <end>00:05:34.07</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I remember, I think it was the first or the second week of our freshman year, my parents will not let me forget this. I called them and I was like, “I don’t belong here. Everyone has taken these things called AP classes, and I never had an AP class, and they all had such high SAT scores and I didn't have- I do not belong here! I don't belong here!'</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:05:34.08</start>
    <end>00:05:37.02</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Your SAT scores were fine.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:05:37.03</start>
    <end>00:05:40.04</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: And then like, I guess I got over it.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:05:40.05</start>
    <end>00:05:41.25</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Yeah, ‘cause we all felt like that.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:05:41.26</start>
    <end>00:05:47.09</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: But it was, like it- The students- they just sort of, you were driven to be. Yeah.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:05:47.10</start>
    <end>00:05:50.26</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And everyone had done a cool thing, 'cause you had just come back from Belgium, remember?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:05:50.27</start>
    <end>00:05:52.05</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Oh yeah, that’s true.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:05:52.06</start>
    <end>00:05:52.24</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Hoooooooh.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:05:52.25</start>
    <end>00:05:53.20</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I was the exchange student.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:05:53.21</start>
    <end>00:06:21.16</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: You were like, “I just spent the last year in Europe,” and I was like, “Oh, I- I worked at a deli.” [Laughing] So yes, everyone was super interesting. Y'know, people were coming in from all over the place and had done all these neat things, so that was- that was really... That was- and yeah, everyone pushed each other to do something interesting. 'Cause you didn't wanna be the one schmuck that was like, 'Whuh,' navel-gazing the entire time.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:06:21.17</start>
    <end>00:06:26.10</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: What was student and campus life like when you were students?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:06:26.11</start>
    <end>00:06:27.21</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Probably much the same.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:06:27.22</start>
    <end>00:06:35.17</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: We- well, maybe... Our first year was- we were on Main fourth and I don’t know about now but back then it was kind of…</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:06:35.18</start>
    <end>00:06:37.23</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: It was like the land of primo real estate up there.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:06:37.24</start>
    <end>00:06:44.16</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah, it really was and our group was just... The whole floor, it's so small that people tend to bond together. It was... a lot of debauchery.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:06:44.17</start>
    <end>00:07:19.13</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And we had... Our class was abnormally large. It was a really large class, so they made doubles into triples so there were a lot of people up there but we bonded really fast and I remember the first, like, month we all moved as like a single unit. And yeah, we were- because we were so tight I think that first year we spent a lot of time like, making our own fun. I mean, neither of us were huge partiers when we first came, so... So, I remember we'd be, like, [Whispered: 'What is this?']</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:07:19.14</start>
    <end>00:07:24.29</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: She like, qualifies that. “When we first came.”</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:07:25.00</start>
    <end>00:07:50.17</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: But yeah, I just remember- I mean.. ‘Cause you didn’t- you’re 18. You’re just figuring it out and figuring out, you know, how to interact with people that’s not in high school. So, the social scene was good ‘cause you could always talk to people and people would always just, like, sit at your dining table, and you’d meet new people. Like Vivek with his name game. Do you remember how Vivek met everybody? It was like, the first two days...</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:07:50.18</start>
    <end>00:08:32.28</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: He would sit down– It- have you- I'm sure, maybe he’s come in– but he’s this like, tall, skinny Indian guy. He had just- it was his first time in the states and he would like, run up to every table, plop himself down and is like, “My name is Vivek. Vivek with a v. V is for victory. Bah blah blah, go.” and you’d have to play the name game around. You’re like, “OK!” and yeah, but then people would like pop up and introduce themselves, so, it started where, like yeah, you just started meeting people and you’d find somebody that you hadn’t met before and then you’d go and meet their whole floor. And there was the parties and all sorts of things, but we were saying that things were much... I don’t know, are they still segregated, sort of, by north/south? I guess there’s east campus now.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:08:32.29</start>
    <end>00:08:35.22</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Still a little bit, but I think it dissipated a little.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:08:35.23</start>
    <end>00:08:45.21</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Really? ‘Cause we’re noticing even now, just the people in our class who are back here, most of south campus was down here at the ice cream social and we walked up and there was all the north campus people.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:08:45.22</start>
    <end>00:09:06.21</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley:  Yesterday, they were mingling and I was like, I was having fun talking to some of the people and I- we walked out today and I was like, "I really would like to go say hi to people, but I have like no place over there." I'm like, “I’m gonna be 32 in a couple weeks; that’s ridiculous! I should be able to talk to whoever the hell I want!" [Whispered: "But I'm still awkward..."]</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:09:06.22</start>
    <end>00:09:12.12</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: How did this like, campus segregation impact social life?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:09:12.13</start>
    <end>00:09:17.11</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I think- I think we’ve stayed, I mean, everyone went to the Harris parties, and.. y'know...</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:09:17.12</start>
    <end>00:09:18.08</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And the movies, and-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:09:18.09</start>
    <end>00:09:26.11</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: But there were definitely like... y’know, the north campus people were into sports and stuff like that and a lot of south campus didn’t do that.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:09:26.12</start>
    <end>00:09:28.03</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: They were into parties, too.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:09:28.04</start>
    <end>00:09:30.23</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: There were the south campus parties and north campus parties.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:09:30.24</start>
    <end>00:09:34.06</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And Bob’s was very segregated and that was always a shame. That was, like...</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:09:34.07</start>
    <end>00:09:36.08</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah, north campus didn’t really go to Bob’s.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:09:36.09</start>
    <end>00:09:42.24</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And they felt... I heard from former managers that North campus felt really ostracized by the whole Bob’s thing-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:09:42.25</start>
    <end>00:09:43.27</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Oh, really?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:09:43.28</start>
    <end>00:09:55.24</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And some of the managers really tried to change that up and put more signs up and bring more people down, but some people were really against that. I was scandalized to find it out. Molly Backes told me.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:09:55.25</start>
    <end>00:09:58.01</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Really? I didn’t know that.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:09:58.02</start>
    <end>00:10:13.12</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: So, I mean I think things are... Once we graduated though, people started, y'know, plans was such a huge deal. It was a big deal when we were here. Prior to it being any web-based email- We were talking today about the VAX system... Back in the day... and plans started as this...</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:10:13.13</start>
    <end>00:10:14.05</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: 'Finger Foley.'</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:10:14.06</start>
    <end>00:10:21.02</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Yeah, 'Finger Bradbury.' And it started just as this way, like, you could stalk people on it, and you could message-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:10:21.03</start>
    <end>00:10:22.04</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: You could chat on there.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:10:22.05</start>
    <end>00:11:00.16</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: You could chat on there. Like, 1997 we were IMing and then it became a big deal elsewhere, and we were like, “Oh, we;ve been doing that for ages.” But because plans was so important, with the VAX, they- Rachel Heck started it up, in what, 2000? 2001 or something. She reconstructed it so that we could all keep in touch. I think that was a huge social shift. I mean, there’s a reason there’s 103 of us from our class here and 99.9% of that is because of plans, and we all keep in contact, and even if we didn’t hang out we know, like I know people’s kids’ names even if I’ve never spoken to them.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:11:00.17</start>
    <end>00:11:06.14</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I know. That’s the big thing. Everyone knows what everyone’s been doing because of either Facebook, or plans. It's really fun.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:11:06.15</start>
    <end>00:11:16.02</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: So yeah, even people that I’ve never spoken to, I know what they’re doing, I know where they are, and then you feel like a weirdo ‘cause you’re like, “Hey how’s that thing? And I… mean…”</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:11:16.03</start>
    <end>00:11:20.26</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: We all plans-stalk. [Laughing]</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:11:20.27</start>
    <end>00:11:32.08</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: But yes, so I think that’s really changed the social scene a bit and even last reunion- I mean, the people that like, come to reunion sort of change your view. Man, I met people at the last reunion that I had never talked to before.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:11:32.09</start>
    <end>00:11:32.14</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury Oh, really?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:11:32.15</start>
    <end>00:11:47.19</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Yeah, and north campus folk, and I didn’t realize until then how stupidly snobby I had been by sticking on south campus as much. But it wasn’t snobbery, it was just out-and-out social anxiety.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:11:47.20</start>
    <end>00:11:55.06</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: How did plans impact student life when you were here, and then as alumni?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:11:55.07</start>
    <end>00:11:57.18</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Well, I think here it was…</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:11:57.19</start>
    <end>00:11:58.04</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Like, song lyrics about your heartbreak and stuff.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:11:58.05</start>
    <end>00:12:16.25</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: It was the beginning of Facebook, y’know? Like, people just posted what they were doing and it was sort of that kind of thing. You’d just post what you were doing, and yeah, you could stalk people that you liked and there was IMing so you could- I don’t remember, how did we find out who was online? You had to do a command and then it would list everyone who was online wasn't it that?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:12:16.26</start>
    <end>00:12:20.21</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: No, you had to actually finger their plan to see if they were on. And then you could…</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:12:20.22</start>
    <end>00:12:24.06</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Oh. Well, that's even more outright stalking.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:12:24.07</start>
    <end>00:12:27.20</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Yeah, and you could see where on campus they were, too.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:12:27.21</start>
    <end>00:12:32.03</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Oh yeah! What computer lab!</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:12:32.04</start>
    <end>00:12:51.29</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And so you could be like, “So and so is here, so if I leave the Forum at this time I can run into them. But it was mostly like, y’know, these heartfelt like, what, y'know, U2 lyrics, and like “Why don’t you love me?” that we thought were oblique and they totally weren’t and you always knew what was happening with people.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:12:52.00</start>
    <end>00:12:53.19</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: But now I turn to plans...</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:12:53.20</start>
    <end>00:12:55.16</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: For advice...</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:12:55.17</start>
    <end>00:13:08.22</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I put things on plans that I would never put on Facebook. People on plans probably know more about my private life than people on Facebook do, but I also go to them for, like if I need information about something.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:13:08.23</start>
    <end>00:13:40.28</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: It’s an advice and sharing.. It’s almost- it's very much a safe place and there was a while, I guess, last year where people were arguing over plans and that got shut down fast, like, 'No, this is a safe place. People come here because there’s nowhere else to go and this is where we support each other,' and it’s the best community. I mean like, everybody’s so supportive. In fact, somebody had an issue- a sort of relatively dangerous domestic issue. People banded together, collected money and set something up so that she could get out.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:13:40.29</start>
    <end>00:13:43.05</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Yeah. Wow.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:13:43.06</start>
    <end>00:14:01.08</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: The, y’know, it’s a good community and it’s sort of strengthened by that, y'know, the community we had here and people still keep track of people they actually hung out with, but I’ve made friends that I wouldn’t have met otherwise over it. In fact I see people now and I’m like, “I just wish I knew your plans name. Oh, that’s what it is, OK!” That's what-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:14:01.09</start>
    <end>00:14:11.14</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Well, we have- There was somebody who was making buttons with your plans username so you could put that on so people would know who you were.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:14:11.15</start>
    <end>00:14:16.21</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: But it turns out most of us actually do know each other, which was impressive.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:14:16.22</start>
    <end>00:14:20.02</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: What are your strongest or best memories of your time at Grinnell?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:14:20.03</start>
    <end>00:14:22.15</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Oh.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:14:22.16</start>
    <end>00:14:33.16</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Well there’s, honestly, my biggest memory, is you bolting off the top bunk. [Laughter] We had, three of us in our room, and-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:14:33.17</start>
    <end>00:14:36.00</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Careful, this might go down for posterity.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:14:36.01</start>
    <end>00:14:41.26</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I know, I know. One of our roommates was... a little-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:14:41.27</start>
    <end>00:14:42.14</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: It was- it was her first time away from home, and no one knew-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:14:42.15</start>
    <end>00:14:50.07</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Procrastinating… Basically she hadn’t washed her sheets in about five months and we were just like, “Hooough.”</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:14:50.08</start>
    <end>00:14:52.05</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: It was a little crazy.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:14:52.06</start>
    <end>00:15:13.26</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: And so one morning she went up- she got up for an eight o’clock class and she left the room and, I was barely awake, just kind of aware that she was leaving the room and she must’ve been just waiting because the moment that door closed she bolts off the top bunk, runs across, strips the bed down, runs down and washes all the sheets and remakes the bed before our roommate got back.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:15:13.27</start>
    <end>00:15:15.28</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Wow.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:15:15.29</start>
    <end>00:15:17.06</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: That’s my most vivid memory.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:15:17.07</start>
    <end>00:15:19.25</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: That one? Geez.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:15:19.26</start>
    <end>00:15:21.19</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Unfortunately, yes</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:15:21.20</start>
    <end>00:15:24.10</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Gosh, I have all sorts of ridiculous- I have so many ridiculous memories.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:15:24.11</start>
    <end>00:15:31.05</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Oh! And crawling up the icy sidewalk on 100 Days with Mary Davis, to French house.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:15:31.06</start>
    <end>00:15:31.22</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: What?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:15:31.23</start>
    <end>00:15:32.27</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: After 100 days party, it was really icy outside-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:15:32.28</start>
    <end>00:15:34.25</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Oh, it was so icy we couldn't get up.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:15:34.26</start>
    <end>00:15:44.21</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: -and we were walking home and there was a slight, y’know, we were a little drunk too, but there was a slight, y'know, sidewalk lift up to the house and so we were walking up and we were slipping all over the place and we finally just, like-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:15:44.22</start>
    <end>00:15:46.03</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: We had to crawl.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:15:46.04</start>
    <end>00:15:47.26</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: -crawled our way up.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:15:47.27</start>
    <end>00:15:53.28</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I remember people slipping and sliding on that little thing down on the side of the Forum, and people like, just skidding out.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:15:53.29</start>
    <end>00:15:56.00</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Someone broke their leg, or two people broke their-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:15:56.01</start>
    <end>00:16:14.11</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Somebody broke their leg on the Burling… oh, no, they slipped and they hit their head, right? Somebody hit their head really bad, and then they had to go home. And then there was leg breaks somewere over there and then there was a bad fall, so yeah, it was like, treacherous out there. But I had so many ridiculously good memories.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:16:14.12</start>
    <end>00:16:20.27</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Oh, I remember when they had to evacuate…</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:16:20.28</start>
    <end>00:16:21.26</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Oh, that’s a bad memory, but yes.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:16:21.27</start>
    <end>00:16:23.19</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yes, that’s a bad memory.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:16:23.20</start>
    <end>00:16:28.21</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: We had a very tragic suicide situation with…</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:16:28.22</start>
    <end>00:16:29.10</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Cyanide.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:16:29.11</start>
    <end>00:16:34.21</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Cyanide. They had to evacuate all of the dorms, and it was really awful.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:16:34.22</start>
    <end>00:16:37.10</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: And a bunch of kids had to go to the hospital.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:16:37.11</start>
    <end>00:16:38.13</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Yeah, it was terrible.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:16:38.14</start>
    <end>00:16:39.24</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: From cyanide poisoning, or-?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:16:39.25</start>
    <end>00:16:41.05</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Well they were worried that they’d been-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:16:41.06</start>
    <end>00:16:50.15</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Because you expell... the gas? So yeah, it was bad. I remember our first year when everyone got the flu, you remember that?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:16:50.16</start>
    <end>00:16:51.08</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: No.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:16:51.09</start>
    <end>00:17:16.20</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: We came back from Christmas break or winter break and we had a Main fourth party. So, there were these Main fourth 40s parties and yeah- All the refrigerator would be filled and the guys next door, Tyler and Brian were gonna bartend and they invited all of campus. And, usually, everybody would just like roll through this party so a good like... I would say several hundred people showed up at that party.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:17:16.21</start>
    <end>00:17:17.10</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I don’t remember.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:17:17.11</start>
    <end>00:17:21.04</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Remember we’d like, poke our heads out, sit in the hallway for ten minutes and then hide back?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:17:21.05</start>
    <end>00:17:23.09</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:17:23.10</start>
    <end>00:17:25.25</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: But, Tyler had gotten the flu. He came back with the flu.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:17:25.26</start>
    <end>00:17:26.23</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Not me; there was a boy on the floor.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:17:26.24</start>
    <end>00:17:55.03</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: The other Tyler. Two Tylers. And he had the flu and he didn’t know it and the next day he was like, “I don’t feel so good,” and it became this, like, crazy carrier monkey thing 'cause he had been bartending and it was, we’d all gotten shots that year, so- or half campus got shots, half campus didn’t. People that got shots were sick for like five days and people that didn’t were sick for two weeks. A third of campus was out at the same time, like, classes had to be canceled...</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:17:55.04</start>
    <end>00:17:55.28</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Really? I don’t remember this at all.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:17:55.29</start>
    <end>00:18:00.15</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: You remember? I had to sleep in that little flip chair in the middle because we were coughing and sneezing too much?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:18:00.16</start>
    <end>00:18:01.27</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah! OK, I do remember that.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:18:01.28</start>
    <end>00:18:29.26</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And we would keep- The coughing was so bad we’d be shaking the bunk bed and wake the other one up, so all of us were just like, in our little sick beds, scattered around the room and oh, it was terrible. I like to share that story with my students when we talk about pathogens. “There was this time…” But I remember- I remember the waltzes and there was that weird year when the, the swing movement came back around so there was tons of swing dancers.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:18:29.27</start>
    <end>00:18:35.06</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Oh yeah! I remember swing dancing with Sierra Soleil. Ah, Sierra.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:18:35.07</start>
    <end>00:18:49.07</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: (Whispered: He was so pretty. Oh god.) And, yeah, all sorts of ridiculous things. I remember, oh, everything, mostly. I remember skinny dippin’ right before graduation.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:18:49.08</start>
    <end>00:18:50.01</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I don't remember that.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:18:50.02</start>
    <end>00:19:04.21</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: You did not come, but we all broke into the PEC and went skinny-dipping. Like, thirty-five people; it was ridiculous. We didn’t get in trouble, though we really should have. And yeah, all sorts of messy, crazy times.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:19:04.22</start>
    <end>00:19:06.20</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: You have such a better memory than I do.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:19:06.21</start>
    <end>00:19:22.00</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Except I don’t ‘cause I'll walk around here and I’m wracked with fear of like, “Yooooou… I…” and people are like, “I remember you did this and you did this and you did this.” (Whispered: I don’t remember any of it.) But I- it was a good time, though.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:19:22.01</start>
    <end>00:19:25.19</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: How has Grinnell changed since you were students?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:19:25.20</start>
    <end>00:19:27.17</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Well, there’s new buildings.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:19:27.18</start>
    <end>00:19:29.08</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Lots of new buildings.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:19:29.09</start>
    <end>00:19:30.02</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Lots of new majors.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:19:30.03</start>
    <end>00:19:30.28</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Really?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:19:30.29</start>
    <end>00:19:31.10</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Are there?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:19:31.11</start>
    <end>00:19:47.25</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah, well there- or, at least, like classes. I was talking to somebody who was saying that they’re doing, they have Arabic classes now and yeah, it’s just, I was in, I was a French major so I’m more aware of those kind of things. But, yeah.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:19:47.26</start>
    <end>00:20:01.24</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I don’t, y’know, it’s so weird ‘cause so it’s so easy to so like, “Kid’s today!” and to have that kind of- which is so strange ’cause we’re not that old. But I remember like the whole- I mean is self-governance still a really big thing here?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:20:01.25</start>
    <end>00:20:02.10</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Yeah.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:20:02.11</start>
    <end>00:20:37.17</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: OK, ‘cause I had gotten some impression that, y’know, there was a little bit more- and maybe it’s a cultural change too, like culturally, that our society has changed so dramatically in the last fifteen years, much more, even more litigious now than it used to be, so everything is sort of micromanaged. I do see that there’s big changes about, y'know, the consumption of an education as students as consumers rather than participants. I haven’t seen that as much here, but walking into that dining hall today freaked me out.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:20:37.18</start>
    <end>00:20:39.00</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Really?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:20:39.01</start>
    <end>00:20:39.28</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And I- Some of it's just like, did you have-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:20:39.29</start>
    <end>00:20:41.02</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Dining hall’s a big change.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:20:41.03</start>
    <end>00:20:53.04</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: It’s nice, it’s great and I was like “This is wonderful,” but there’s like, y’know that sort of old lady-like, “Back in my day we ate what they served us and we liked it,” kind of, and…</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:20:53.05</start>
    <end>00:20:55.15</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Why? What was so… oh, because they got some new choices?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:20:55.16</start>
    <end>00:20:56.09</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Have you seen it?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:20:56.10</start>
    <end>00:20:56.22</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: No.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:20:56.23</start>
    <end>00:21:08.11</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: There’s a pizza bar, and like a stir fry bar and a deli bar and a salad bar and hot food and ice cream and a thing, and another thing… and, but it’s like…</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:21:08.12</start>
    <end>00:21:12.05</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: We had a cereal bar and a salad bar and a dessert bar and then we had the food.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:21:12.06</start>
    <end>00:21:25.02</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: But you could eat, like- the food is like nine different kinds of food things. So you could have all of these other things and not choose between your CPP or your vegan CPP.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:21:25.03</start>
    <end>00:21:28.28</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: There’s no longer a little menu of what’s being served every day?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:21:28.29</start>
    <end>00:21:37.27</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: There's one, like, posted outside the dining hall but it’s got like, vegan option, pasta option, pizza option.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:21:37.28</start>
    <end>00:21:40.05</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley:  Oh, there’s a pasta bar too. Wow.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:21:40.06</start>
    <end>00:21:45.10</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I guess, y’know I wasn’t in the dining halls ‘cause I moved off to French house and I went off campus.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:21:45.11</start>
    <end>00:21:46.14</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Oh, that's true.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:21:46.15</start>
    <end>00:22:01.22</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: So I don’t remember that. But I didn't think that having one dining hall must make- ‘cause that was the thing about the segregation between north and south campus was, y’know north campus ate at Cowles, south campus ate at Quad, and yeah... There wasn’t a lot of crossover.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:22:01.23</start>
    <end>00:22:05.07</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: From what I’ve heard it’s definitely more unified, eating at the dining hall.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:22:05.08</start>
    <end>00:22:44.06</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Which is cool. I think that’s a good thing. Part of me wonders about, you know, just general resilience and like, wow y’know you, this is what you’re doing and you just have to do it and there are certain acceptance things and then not being able to always get what you want when you want it kind of thing. Part of that is because now I’m teaching and I’m like, 'Goddamn kids today.'
But, I mean at the same time it's still- they would say that about us, too. I think everyone’s always like, “We were the greatest generation,” and at the same time that’s not true. People come to Grinnell because it’s a good school, but also because there’s this vibe here.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:22:44.07</start>
    <end>00:23:02.03</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: We were looking at the ’06, ’05 cluster and were like, 'We feel like we should know them even though we don't, because they look like us.' And you guys look like us. It’s been really funny like, “Oh, right. OK, just a little time difference, alright.”</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:23:02.04</start>
    <end>00:23:10.06</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: How do you feel- like- self-governance impacted your lives while you were here?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:23:10.07</start>
    <end>00:23:40.25</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I know, well, I was always very aware of responsibility kind of person but I think that when I talk with my friends who went to schools that were like a state school where there was rules and things they could and couldn’t do, there was a whole lot more rebelling in them than I feel we ever really had because there was nothing to rebel against here and so we focused on different things whereas there it was like, "What can we get away with?" or, "What can’t we do?"</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:23:40.26</start>
    <end>00:24:05.16</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And there, we were really conscious of it here. Remember when they changed the alcohol awareness stuff during orientation? ‘Cause when we came in they did that, like, 'How to Take Care of Drunk People' kind of shtick but then the insurance policies changed on campus, so when somebody was sick you had to call the ambulance, and if the ambulance got called there was a police report and it became this huge deal and like, it was a big town 'n gown conflict…</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:24:05.17</start>
    <end>00:24:09.00</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Well that was the beginning of a lot of that binge-drinking concerns in college, just in general.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:24:09.01</start>
    <end>00:24:51.23</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Right, but they weren’t doing the sort of how-to-take-care-of-your-friends spiel anymore and I remember everybody got really up in arms because, us coming in was, "All right, well people are gonna do dumb stuff," ‘cause you’re 18, 19, 20 years old and that just happens. "But, here’s how to look out for each other, here’s what to keep in mind." You didn’t have that same cultural philosophy, but you also didn’t have the same sort of like, you just let your friend go. When they changed that, y’know it was ingrained in you immediately. So we were very conscious of that sort of self-governance and we were like, "You’re being super drunk. Let's carry you somewhere and make sure you’re fine."</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:24:51.24</start>
    <end>00:25:20.23</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: But also just, being able- on dorms floors. Like our floor, we had to vote for whether or not it was smoking, and we also got to vote on if it was co-ed or not, co-ed bathrooms you know, and those kinds of things it was just sort of like that- it kind of installed that idea of, y’know, you can choose but you need to be responsible about your choices and respect what the choice becomes, even if it’s not exactly what you want.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:25:20.24</start>
    <end>00:25:26.11</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Yeah, and being conscientious for the people you lived with. I remember we were all like really conscientious. I mean, there'd always be-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:25:26.12</start>
    <end>00:25:27.28</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah, respectful of each other.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:25:27.29</start>
    <end>00:26:16.26</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I mean, obviously people had different, idiosyncratic sort of quirks, if they forget to clean stuff themself. But at the same time everyone was really like, "Ok we’re gonna talk about it," if there was a problem we would just, "Dude, what are you doing? Don’t do that. That’s messed up." Or y’know, "Please pick your underpants up. They've been stuck to this spot. It’s bothering me," and people would be like, "Oh yeah, ok cool," because there would be a back and forth. My sister is a college sophomore now and she has problems and I was like, "Well did she talk to-" Like, ah, they hate the girl next door, They’re gonna go talk to the dean about it ‘cause she’s so loud. I was like, “Oh, well did they have conversations with her?” “Oh, I don’t know.” “Did they talk to the RA?” “Oh, I don’t know.” I was like, well there’s a chain of command here.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:26:16.27</start>
    <end>00:26:19.11</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Why don't you just talk about it?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:26:19.12</start>
    <end>00:26:29.04</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley:  Why don’t you just talk about it and everyone vote on something? God! So I think that was really good for us because we’re a much more conscientious bunch.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:26:29.05</start>
    <end>00:26:34.04</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: How do you feel like your class was distinct from classes before or classes after you?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:26:34.05</start>
    <end>00:26:36.27</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Oh that’s a good question.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:26:36.28</start>
    <end>00:26:40.09</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Well she was saying that she thinks our class is highly attractive now.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:26:40.10</start>
    <end>00:26:42.09</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: We are a very attractive bunch!</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:26:42.10</start>
    <end>00:26:44.09</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: She was saying that.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:26:44.10</start>
    <end>00:26:54.24</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I mean, really. I think we’re much more bonded as a class. I think part of that is plans, because people do stay in touch.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:26:54.25</start>
    <end>00:27:01.12</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: We were one of the first classes that graduated with plans being available to graduates.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:27:01.13</start>
    <end>00:27:17.28</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And it was very much our thing too, as like a little unit. I think... we were a little bit more cohesive because of that, I think. I don’t think, while we were here we were super different were we?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:27:17.29</start>
    <end>00:27:20.21</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I don’t think so. Though, a lot of the younger years…</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:27:20.22</start>
    <end>00:27:23.15</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Everyone said we were slightly less fun, but I don’t think that was the case.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:27:23.16</start>
    <end>00:27:37.24</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: A lot of younger years- A few people from like 2003, 2002 are here just because it’s our ten year reunion and they wanna be with us. But I don’t know if that has anything, I don’t know if we really…</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:27:37.25</start>
    <end>00:27:55.24</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I think our distinction is since then we’ve been, I think one of the best classes about keeping in touch. Which again, 130 people. They were pretty, they were like, “Let’s see if we can break a record! 70, 80 people!” And we're like, "Boomf! Done!"</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:27:55.25</start>
    <end>00:27:59.01</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs:  What transitions did you see during your time here?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:27:59.02</start>
    <end>00:28:04.07</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Well, there was the different focus on…</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:28:04.08</start>
    <end>00:28:05.21</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Yeah, the self-governance was...</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:28:05.22</start>
    <end>00:28:08.12</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah, self-governance. What other transitions?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:28:08.13</start>
    <end>00:28:57.07</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: There was a big... It was, again, because of the educational sort of cultural push in academia, that really 'Let's get us into the top ten,' that became a much more of a thing, and focusing on the endowment and focusing on the college as a business rather than as this sort of idealistic, "Oh we’re here for learning and anarchy," and that became a lot less of a focus. That sort of, hyper-liberalism of, "Let’s shake things up. Let’s do these crazy things," and I would wager that the classes, the older classes here probably look at our classes as being a lot more conservative because we just didn’t have that. Right? Like that sort of ideology of revolution, as much.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:28:57.08</start>
    <end>00:29:00.18</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Well yeah, yeah. But there was a lot of activism on campus.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:29:00.19</start>
    <end>00:29:00.29</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: There was.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:29:01.00</start>
    <end>00:29:28.11</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: It was, I think, I don’t remember enough about this but I remember there being a lot of stuff against- Like there seemed to be, I think, I know global development studies wasn’t new at that point but I felt like it was becoming- it was... being more developed as things were going on? I think we were getting a little bit more focused on global, and there was a lot of y’know, the sweatshop movement was while we were here.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:29:28.12</start>
    <end>00:29:30.19</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: That was really big, yeah.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:29:30.20</start>
    <end>00:29:36.09</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: And… what else do I remember?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:29:36.10</start>
    <end>00:29:38.03</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I’m sure there was a Coca-Cola thing at some point.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:29:38.04</start>
    <end>00:29:47.14</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: No, it was the sweat shops. It was all sweat shops. It was getting the bookstore to stop buying brands. But that’s all…</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:29:47.15</start>
    <end>00:29:49.05</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: We were here for the election, too.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:29:49.06</start>
    <end>00:29:50.00</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: What election?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:29:50.01</start>
    <end>00:29:51.03</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Bush election.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:29:51.04</start>
    <end>00:29:56.21</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Oh yeah you- but that was our senior year, right? I wasn’t here for it, I was in France.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:29:56.22</start>
    <end>00:30:00.12</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: What was the atmosphere like after the election, or leading up to it?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:30:00.13</start>
    <end>00:30:01.14</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah, I wanna know too.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:30:01.15</start>
    <end>00:30:19.29</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley:  Despondent. I mean, everyone was so pumped, but nobody thought Bush stood a chance so people weren’t even worried about voting for Gore. People were voting for Nader because Bush was so goddamned stupid, so why would you worry about this guy getting in? Oh my God, what a mess.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:30:20.00</start>
    <end>00:30:22.12</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: What happened, what did people do afterwards?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:30:22.13</start>
    <end>00:31:11.23</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I- There were tears. I remember people crying in lounges. So, everyone was like gathered in the lounge and people were crying and it was like, the end of the world. Which, ultimately, not super wrong. [Laughing] So, y’know, good on us for seeing that happen, but yes. But it was, that was a mess. I remember everyone was like, really motivated to get, y’know. We all went and voted at the school over, wherever that is- over there. But, but yeah, it was just shock, like, “What?” It was like watching every idealistic bubble of, “I have faith in our country,” just go boof! “But he’s so stupid! Everyone else must be stupid, too! What?!” This was the first time you realized you lived in a bubble.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:31:11.24</start>
    <end>00:31:27.09</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I was abroad in France with a program from a much more conservative school, and they were all really happy. I was like, “Aaaaaah!”</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:31:27.10</start>
    <end>00:31:41.06</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: It was the first time, I think, a lot of people realized that this is a bubble and the people that you talk to here and the things that you encounter everyday are not necessarily normative on a huge cultural scale.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:31:41.07</start>
    <end>00:31:41.21</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:31:41.22</start>
    <end>00:32:09.26</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: What’s normative here is very different elsewhere. A friend of ours was just talking and she had been on some sort of, like, was hanging out with some friends and she was like, “Let’s just cuddle, and like lay down and cuddle.” They were like, “That’s really weird,” she was like, “Really?” I was like, “Yes, nobody does that anymore ‘cause we did that in our crazy little like, 'Let’s all socialize in bed.'” That’s not normal.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:32:09.27</start>
    <end>00:32:17.00</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah, that’s true, there’s a lot of learning about what was mainstream, after getting out of Grinnell.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:32:17.01</start>
    <end>00:32:24.20</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: “You mean everyone wears clothes here? I don't- I don't understand... All the time?"</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:32:24.21</start>
    <end>00:32:28.21</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: What memories or images do you have of the town of Grinnell?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:32:28.22</start>
    <end>00:32:31.21</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: So many.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:32:31.22</start>
    <end>00:32:32.29</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Cafe Phoenix.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:32:33.00</start>
    <end>00:32:52.10</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Café Phoenix, which, I got to work there. It was really fun. I went the other day, and he remembered me! He was like, “I was just talking about you! They were talking about the chattiest waitress we ever had!” Like, “I’m sorry, I never shut up.” But yeah, Café Phoenix, the farmer’s market eventually.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:32:52.11</start>
    <end>00:32:56.26</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I remember going to the thrift store that was over…</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:32:56.27</start>
    <end>00:32:57.22</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: By the farmer’s market?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:32:57.23</start>
    <end>00:32:58.13</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: No.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:32:58.14</start>
    <end>00:32:59.06</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: By Cafe Phoenix?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:32:59.07</start>
    <end>00:33:01.07</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: No.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:33:01.08</start>
    <end>00:33:01.12</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Which one?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:33:01.13</start>
    <end>00:33:02.16</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Wasn’t it on the other side? It was… we know the...</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:33:02.17</start>
    <end>00:33:04.26</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: There was that little building in that park.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:33:04.27</start>
    <end>00:33:05.16</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Down the hill.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:33:05.17</start>
    <end>00:33:05.24</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: In the basement...</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:33:05.25</start>
    <end>00:33:06.06</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah!</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:33:06.07</start>
    <end>00:33:13.08</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Yeah. We spent so much time in these thrift stores, remember? We had everything; weird mismatched clothes.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:33:13.09</start>
    <end>00:33:18.05</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Oh and I remember driving… oh I guess that’s Iowa City, but going there for Disco clothes.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:33:18.06</start>
    <end>00:33:26.28</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Yes! And I remember.. I was just thinking that, in your little tiny Toyota and remember we would be like, “There’s that house on the hill. We have like fifteen more minutes!”</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:33:26.29</start>
    <end>00:33:33.03</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: But the town of Grinnell, I remember, what else do I remember about Grinnell?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:33:33.04</start>
    <end>00:34:29.23</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I remember when McNally's started changing, ‘cause it used to be much more mom ‘n pop, but then it started getting a little bit more cosmopolitan, but I remember first movin’ here in ’97 and like, this is a snobby thing to say, but the Midwest was really different back then. It was a good ten years behind what was happening on the coasts and it was a much more like, middle America, kind of, 'These are the things that we eat here,' and things have become much more homogenized, sort of food-wise, across the country. So, but at the time like, you couldn’t get all of this stuff at all and you'd be like, “But where’s the things that I’m used to eating?” And it was all this really local- I mean, it was great ‘cause was all this sort of local, cultural stuff but I remember that changing. I remember the pub before it was no more. What else did we do?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:34:29.24</start>
    <end>00:34:39.22</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I remember one summer I house sat for someone I worked for. I worked in the library. I house sat for one of those people and I was off in a community that I was never in.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:34:39.23</start>
    <end>00:34:42.00</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Where was that?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:34:42.01</start>
    <end>00:34:47.03</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: It was over west of the road that brings us into town.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:34:47.04</start>
    <end>00:34:49.10</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Oh yeah, I remember that.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:34:49.11</start>
    <end>00:34:56.13</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah, it was an interesting… it was like the first time I had actually lived in town. It was fun.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:34:56.14</start>
    <end>00:35:07.21</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Yeah, that was fun. I remember, we used to take all those walks out into the countryside, remember? And ride our bike, when we had bikes. Every so often we had a bike, and I don’t know...</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:35:07.22</start>
    <end>00:35:11.16</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I don’t remember. I didn’t have a bike. We walked, you and I did.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:35:11.17</start>
    <end>00:35:15.27</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: We walked a lot, yeah. So we would walk out to the country roads, which was beautiful out there. It was nice.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:35:15.28</start>
    <end>00:35:18.14</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: That was where my yearbook picture came from!</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:35:18.15</start>
    <end>00:35:20.16</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury and Allison Foley: Yeah!</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:35:20.17</start>
    <end>00:35:21.16</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I took that yearbook picture.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:35:21.17</start>
    <end>00:35:22.05</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I know!</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:35:22.06</start>
    <end>00:35:26.06</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: And you took my yearbook picture. We were a team.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:35:26.07</start>
    <end>00:35:30.19</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: What are your favorite places in Grinnell, either on the campus or in town?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:35:30.20</start>
    <end>00:35:34.22</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: The library. Love the library.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:35:34.23</start>
    <end>00:35:38.10</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Bob’s. Spent a lot of time in Bob’s.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:35:38.11</start>
    <end>00:35:48.20</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: ARH. Like, I walked in here. This is the first time I think I’ve been in ARH since I graduated and was like, “Oh God I remember this, like, feels good.”</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:35:48.21</start>
    <end>00:36:04.16</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I used to spend a lot of time in that Isaiah room upstairs. The classics room at the end of the hall that has like that- I spent, I took so many classes in that room and I just like, gaze at it longingly. But yeah, there and God, so many times in Bob’s and...</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:36:04.17</start>
    <end>00:36:06.02</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Up by the Observatory.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:36:06.03</start>
    <end>00:36:14.24</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: By the Observatory is nice. The Cleveland computer lab. I spent many, many, many hours in there. Many. And quad.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:36:14.25</start>
    <end>00:36:15.24</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Quad.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:36:15.25</start>
    <end>00:36:16.06</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I love Quad.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:36:16.07</start>
    <end>00:36:19.07</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: And Main lounge. Gardner.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:36:19.08</start>
    <end>00:36:21.07</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: We didn’t spend much time in Main Lounge, though.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:36:21.08</start>
    <end>00:36:23.18</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: We didn’t? I remember playing the piano there a lot.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:36:23.19</start>
    <end>00:36:44.01</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: You used to play the piano there a lot, but I was never really... But, Gardner, I went down there quite a bunch. "Quite a bunch," good grammar Foley. And Harris. I liked the Harris parties, ‘cause you could go dancing. That was always fun. Where else did we go? I honestly don’t know what the hell we did. Oh, the Forum! I was in the Forum all the time, too.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:36:44.02</start>
    <end>00:37:05.07</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Oh, the red kind of basket chairs in the Forum. I have a cup that has, what d’you call that, a silhouette of those chairs and the round thing on it. Yeah! I don’t know who- she used to do postcards or something, and it was on a cup and that’s my Grinnell cup.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:37:05.08</start>
    <end>00:37:11.17</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: We spent a lot of time in the Forum ‘cause that’s where you would go to see and be seen, so... We would leave our-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:37:11.18</start>
    <end>00:37:12.21</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury:  Sometimes to go read.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:37:12.22</start>
    <end>00:37:25.19</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: We have to go take the rounds, and like make the rounds, sit and read for a little bit and scope everybody out and y’know, yeah. Then you move to the library to go find people there. I don’t know when we got any work done, like, I would pretend to do work, but really I was just people-watching.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:37:25.20</start>
    <end>00:37:46.19</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: See, that’s funny. I was thinking, I would go to the Forum to read because I could focus more in there, on reading if there was noise around me. Then I go to the library to really study, or ARH, the study carrels in ARH. And then, yeah, I remember a lot more homework than socializing.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:37:46.20</start>
    <end>00:37:48.04</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I did a lot of homework!</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:37:48.05</start>
    <end>00:37:49.25</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I know, but that’s what I remember.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:37:49.26</start>
    <end>00:38:00.01</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I didn’t do as much as I should’ve done, but I also didn’t party as much as I should’ve done too, so I don’t know what I did. I talked to everybody. A lot. That’s pretty much what I did.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:38:00.02</start>
    <end>00:38:02.25</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah that's true, it would take us a long time to go anywhere.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:38:02.26</start>
    <end>00:38:11.26</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Still does. What else did we do? That’s the gist of it.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:38:11.27</start>
    <end>00:38:18.12</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I remember, Brenda Wiler concerts and Morphine.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:38:18.13</start>
    <end>00:38:19.09</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I don't rememeber that.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:38:19.10</start>
    <end>00:38:20.23</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I remember the Morphine concert.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:38:20.24</start>
    <end>00:38:27.21</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Oh, kinda remember that! We talked about, did you go to the Black Eyed Peas? No, ‘cause you weren’t here senior year. We went to the Black Eyed Peas, they played-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:38:27.22</start>
    <end>00:38:29.18</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Here? Wow.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:38:29.19</start>
    <end>00:39:14.05</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And it was pre-Fregie and the hip people knew and were like, “We should really go.” I was dating this guy who knew everything about music, I thought. He was like, "We really have to go to this." We go and it's up at Harris and there’s like 25 people. Thy're just like, people milling around like, “Mm OK.” They were good but it was like, “Oh, all right.” I remember afterwards people were getting real flirty with them, and it was hilarious. It was just like, "What is going on?" ‘Cause I didn’t know that they were a big deal and I guess it was another year or two before they really hit it huge. But people knew about them and it was very much a like, “We’re gonna go hook up with the Black Eyed Peas!” And so they did. (Whispered: And they got kicked out of the hotel.)</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:39:14.06</start>
    <end>00:39:15.10</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: The Black Eyed Peas did?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:39:15.11</start>
    <end>00:39:16.06</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: No.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:39:16.07</start>
    <end>00:39:17.21</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: The people did.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:39:17.22</start>
    <end>00:39:26.25</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Mhm hm, and they had to walk back to campus! Scandal! This is terrible.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:39:26.26</start>
    <end>00:39:30.14</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: What was the role of technology on campus?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:39:30.15</start>
    <end>00:39:42.00</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Well, the VAX. We had the VAX. When we first came here… I mean honestly, when I first, I had had email for about two years before I came to Grinnell.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:39:42.01</start>
    <end>00:39:55.19</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I hadn’t at all. In fact I knew about it because my high school boyfriend was like, computer guy and he was like, “I have this modem thing.” I was like, “So it’s like a phone call between computers? Explain more!”</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:39:55.20</start>
    <end>00:40:12.09</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I knew about it because my parents were with the school in my town and so they had a connection through the high school, but really the VAX system- Our first email was on DOS and then – how old do we sound?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:40:12.10</start>
    <end>00:40:17.10</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: But then everybody used the computer labs but then you came back from winter break that year with a computer.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:40:17.11</start>
    <end>00:40:17.25</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah. We had Ethernet cards.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:40:17.26</start>
    <end>00:40:29.07</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And so there was a computer in the room and it was such a big deal. You had, oh, Oregon Trail and everyone would-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:40:29.08</start>
    <end>00:40:29.28</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: The whole floor.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:40:29.29</start>
    <end>00:40:36.28</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: -would gather around the common room, y'know, all the people on the floor and we’d all sit in a little row and play Oregon Trail together. It was awesome.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:40:36.29</start>
    <end>00:40:58.26</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: It was really, like, if you think about what we use the computer for now, it was- The technology was writing papers, it was checking your email. I know that it got big when we could store our own files and retrieve them, and not have to carry around floppy disks. But, internet wasn’t a big thing.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:40:58.27</start>
    <end>00:41:03.07</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: It wasn’t a big thing at all. I remember looking things up sort of by the end, and looking stuff up.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:41:03.08</start>
    <end>00:41:08.06</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I remember hearing about Facebook, but it was just for another school and we were all like “oh.”</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:41:08.07</start>
    <end>00:41:09.16</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: No, no, no that was after we left.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:41:09.17</start>
    <end>00:41:10.20</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Really?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:41:10.21</start>
    <end>00:41:18.03</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Yeah, ‘cause I remember somebody on plans was like, “Have you guys ever heard of this Facebook thing?” and I thought it was like the new student like, lookbook.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:41:18.04</start>
    <end>00:41:25.12</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah! That’s what I thought too because you get those little, the freshman’s, or, New Year's, we'd get- and I thought that was Facebook.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:41:25.13</start>
    <end>00:41:26.17</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: But that was after we left.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:41:26.18</start>
    <end>00:41:27.14</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Really?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:41:27.15</start>
    <end>00:41:27.25</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Yeah.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:41:27.26</start>
    <end>00:41:28.27</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Oh. Well.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:41:28.28</start>
    <end>00:41:34.10</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: It was like, ’05 that that started, right? I don't remember. I didn’t see the movie.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:41:34.11</start>
    <end>00:41:38.16</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: But It wasn’t for internet. It was research on the, in the computer but-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:41:38.17</start>
    <end>00:42:28.18</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And even then you could sort of look stuff up but you couldn’t find journal articles online. That didn’t exist yet. So, you could find things- there was that automated system in the library where you could type in a keyword and it would tell you what journals it mainly had and then you would check the card catalogue to see if the journals were there. And then you would spend, I remember spending days on the third floor of the library going through and getting journals and looking through the index of those and just copying articles on the photo- spent hundreds of dollars on the stupid photocopier. It was completely different. If you needed to know something you had to go and look it up. Our brains changed since then, and that’s tricky. We were just talking the other day too, two people had cell phones on campus.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:42:28.19</start>
    <end>00:42:35.22</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah, and it was like, “They have a cell phone? Who do they think they are?” Y’know? And it was sort of like,  "Why do you have that?"</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:42:35.23</start>
    <end>00:43:07.26</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I don’t remember who the other person was- I know Trey Reis had one, and he was like, super hip guy, and I remember he was on the cell phone, in Quad once, and Robin Kimble was like, “Put your phone away you fucking snob!” and they were good friends, so it was OK. But it was like, 'cause we were like "Who the hell would you need to call? It’s all on campus." We all knew each other’s extensions and you’d just call and if you didn’t see them and they weren’t at home then you would just see them at the Forum. You never needed to know where somebody was at any given moment. So, yeah I remember that. And now, phones- glued to our phones. I mean I have mine now-</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:43:07.27</start>
    <end>00:43:13.07</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I know, we’re both have our cell phones, and everybody, everyone’s got their iPhone, y’know?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:43:13.08</start>
    <end>00:43:14.23</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: If you don’t text them back within five minutes...</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:43:14.24</start>
    <end>00:43:21.26</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah! And now, y’know, it’s not even that it’s like, “Oh, where’s James?” “Oh, I don’t know, I’ll go find him.”</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:43:21.27</start>
    <end>00:43:51.07</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I can’t be bothered to walk a half a block see if he’s lingering where I think he’s lingering. But, so it was a totally different thing. I mean, the way our brains changed in just processing information, but also the way we’ve changed socially is, I mean it’s enhanced it obviously but at the same time it's much more, “I need to see you this second,” or, y’know. There’s no element of surprise anymore. Our friend Gant, remember? I used to like, Gant and I would like think about each other.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:43:51.08</start>
    <end>00:43:51.22</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: And then find eachother.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:43:51.23</start>
    <end>00:43:55.18</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And then we'd magically find each other within seconds. And now we don’t get to do that anymore.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:43:55.19</start>
    <end>00:43:56.12</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: You can still text each other.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:43:56.13</start>
    <end>00:44:25.28</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: We need to just play hide and seek in Burling again.  But yeah, it was really different. But it just exploded all, after that, so, I (you guys had a totally different experience. I saw something on Burling like, something on Burling bathrooms and they were like, “Things I like about you,” and one of ‘em was like, “Sweet text messages you sent.” I was like, “I guess you would text each other like, ‘I like you.”’ But instead we all just like, whispered to each other.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:44:25.29</start>
    <end>00:44:28.10</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Or we plans-ed each other.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:44:28.11</start>
    <end>00:44:33.26</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Or wrote weirdo U2 lyrics on our plans and you just had to know who it meant.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:44:33.27</start>
    <end>00:44:35.19</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Did you have secrets on plans?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:44:35.20</start>
    <end>00:44:36.12</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley and Tyler Bradbury: No.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:44:36.13</start>
    <end>00:44:37.11</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: That was totally new, too.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:44:37.12</start>
    <end>00:44:43.29</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: That didn't happen. No, if- We were just talking about that, that was basically Burling basement bathroom. Y’know, like, if you have a secret, you write it on the door.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:44:44.00</start>
    <end>00:44:47.05</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Is that a big thing here?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:44:47.06</start>
    <end>00:44:47.24</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: The bathrooms?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:44:47.25</start>
    <end>00:44:48.27</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: No, the secrets.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:44:48.28</start>
    <end>00:45:16.04</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Sometimes it- There are some core people who read them every week. Some people get pissed if they aren’t updated right on time, and sometimes it, someone posts an inflammatory secret and people get angry about it. Yeah. But it’s just been, like, the divide between plans and the real world. Plans stuff stays on plans and real stuff... yeah?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:45:16.05</start>
    <end>00:45:23.09</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I’m finding that a lot of people now are posting things and putting a “Please don’t share on Facebook” or... y'know, might crossover.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:45:23.10</start>
    <end>00:45:29.06</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Right. "My family doesn’t know," or this, so if you read it here, keep it here.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:45:29.07</start>
    <end>00:45:31.21</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: What were your favorite academic experiences at Grinnell?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:45:31.22</start>
    <end>00:45:42.29</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: (Whispered: Favorite academic experience?) I loved my, see I can just jump in right here. I loved my French, what d’you call those..?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:45:43.00</start>
    <end>00:45:43.27</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Seminars?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:45:43.28</start>
    <end>00:45:45.01</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Seminars, yeah.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:45:45.02</start>
    <end>00:45:45.07</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: (Whispered: Oh, you do have those.)</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:45:45.08</start>
    <end>00:45:59.00</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Because I only had four people in my seminars and it sucks sometimes ‘cause there’s a two hour seminar and there’s four of us and one person hasn’t done the reading and so I'm like, “C’mon dude, this is your 25 minutes a day.”</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:45:59.01</start>
    <end>00:46:01.01</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Who did you have? ‘Cause I’m also a French major.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:46:01.02</start>
    <end>00:46:15.00</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I had Jan Gross, who’s in Ireland, Monsieur Moisan, and David Harrison came right before I left. And then Mr. Gross was, Dan Gross was there. Yeah, and Jan was my advisor.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:46:15.01</start>
    <end>00:46:17.24</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: David Harrison’s my advisor.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:46:17.25</start>
    <end>00:46:33.07</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Oh yeah? Well good! Yeah, most of my French seminars, I loved my French seminars, and especially Jan Gross’s seventeenth century, French Literature and Culture. Oh God that was the best class I took there.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:46:33.08</start>
    <end>00:46:35.01</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: When did you take that?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:46:35.02</start>
    <end>00:46:38.23</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: My junior, sophomore or junior year. It was one of my first seminars.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:46:38.24</start>
    <end>00:46:50.10</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I just remember you camped out on that couch in our room in French House, and you threw, oh, you knitted the thing for it crocheted a thing for it. You didn’t – well, we’ll get back to that, what happened to that couch.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:46:50.11</start>
    <end>00:46:51.25</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: No. No one will wanna know.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:46:51.26</start>
    <end>00:46:54.24</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: It was a good story. Yes you do 'cause I almost got expelled for it.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:46:54.25</start>
    <end>00:46:56.12</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Oh! I didn't even know.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:46:56.13</start>
    <end>00:47:45.27</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: But no, I just remember you camped out with those little books. Anyway, the couch, we sold it when we moved out, like the day. We were just like, put it out on the curb or whatever we did, we sold it to somebody for a dollar, it was a big gray couch. I guess, we left like, got a moving van, drove home or did whatever. Drove back to New Jersey. That night the couch was burned somewhere on campus, but it was identified as my couch and so there was this like, apparently without me knowing anything about it, like an investigation was kind of launched and they were talking about, oh you know, vandalism, and expelling me. Then someone was like, “She’s in New Jersey, she didn’t do it!” But I didn’t find out until months later. I came back and everyone was like, “You came this close to getting kicked out of school.” I was like, "What!"</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:47:45.28</start>
    <end>00:48:45.06</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: But yeah, I had a lot of good, y’know I think about the sort of most fun... I was a Psych major, originally, and then I switched. I was Psych and Classics, and then, now I do Anthropology. I remember it being senior year and being in one of the archeology classes, and John Whittaker would have these like, bags of stuff that they kind of excavated in the thirties. Not the thirties: that’s crazy pants. But like, in the seventies, like late seventies bag of dirt that had never been shifted and so it was this class project, of like, 'OK they’re gonna rummage through.' We ended up pulling out, like, bits of human bone. That’s what I do now, but that was the very first time I had ever experienced that and I was so like, “This is awesome!” I was so excited and that was like a real pivotal moment and that’s why Paul bought me those books on dead people archeology and that’s why I’m doing what I’m doing today. For better or for worse.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:48:45.07</start>
    <end>00:49:39.19</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: But, that was- The most useful thing that ever happened, ever, was in my first semester. I was taking some class on like, Gods and mythology or something or other and I remember the first paper we had to do was a one page, explain the role of the Gods in the Iliad. One page. Terrible assignment. There were tears, people were handing in things with like eight point font with stuff like up the side. It was ridiculous and the whole point of it was to torture us to try to write concisely. Y’know, don’t just blah everything all over the page. I tell my students that all the time. “If you can write something concisely then you can always fluff it out later. But if you’re doing something that's short, every word has to count.” So that was by far the best lesson I ever learned.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:49:39.20</start>
    <end>00:50:31.17</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: My most defining class was Chinese history with Andrew Che, because he, I forget, how did it happen? He was my professor and so I knew who he was and then in the Scarlet and Black there was an advertisement for a school in China looking for an English teacher, my senior year, and I had applied for the French assistantship and had been wait-listed because the department nominated someone and I didn’t realize I could’ve just applied through the program directly and gone anyway. So I was wait-listed and I was kinda like, “Oh no, what am I gonna do. I'm getting ready to graduate,” and I saw that and because I’d known... I knew him and he was my professor, I went and talked to him about it and I ended up, that’s where I went after graduation, spent a year in China teaching. That was the beginning of my career.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:50:31.18</start>
    <end>00:50:32.14</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: There you go!</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:50:32.15</start>
    <end>00:50:38.25</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I still do that, ten years later. I’m still teaching English as a second language.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:50:38.26</start>
    <end>00:50:55.03</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: If you were writing a history of Grinnell College, what events from your time would you include? Or not events, but y’know, social atmosphere, what would you include?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:50:55.04</start>
    <end>00:50:58.12</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: That’s a really hard question.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:50:58.13</start>
    <end>00:50:59.04</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs:  Yeah, I know.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:50:59.05</start>
    <end>00:51:45.04</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Y’know I don’t know that I can think of any... overall ones because I think everyone’s experiences here are so individualistic. I mean, we’re obviously, we were close and we’re obviously still close now but our college experiences were completely different, even if we lived together for two years. I don’t know why they’re so different but they really are. I mean, we hung out all the time. So, even going through the sort of same thing, I think people had very different ideas. I’m learning things about people now, like, "Really? That was your experience? I had no idea." I think there are things that are completely shared that are universal. Like that feeling that, “I don’t belong here and I’m not smart enough.” Remember Matt Belknap's song?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:51:45.05</start>
    <end>00:51:46.01</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Stupid, Feeling Stupid at Grinnell?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:51:46.02</start>
    <end>00:51:49.22</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Feeling Stupid at Grinnell. It was very sweet. He has four kids, by the way.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:51:49.23</start>
    <end>00:51:52.05</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I know, I just found out about that.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:51:52.06</start>
    <end>00:51:54.05</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: With that girl, I don’t remember her name.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:51:54.06</start>
    <end>00:51:54.25</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I don’t either.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:51:54.26</start>
    <end>00:52:24.27</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: That one. (Whispered: The one that was mean to everybody. That was terrible.) Oh, gossipy. But yeah, he did the thing at Bob’s and he was like, “Well, I wrote a song about my first semester here,” and it was this really cute, charming, like, "All of my friends also applied to Harvard and they all have- their parents all have PhDs and I’m just this schmuck  who's trying to get by." We were like, “Yes! That is so true!”</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:52:24.28</start>
    <end>00:52:30.23</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Everyone thought that. I can’t think of any one, big thing. I</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:52:30.24</start>
    <end>00:52:45.11</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: think, I mean I think the big, the waltzes and things were always a big thing collectively. I still get stuck on the Bob’s exotic dance night, which I somehow went to every single time without meaning to, always while studying for a final.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:52:45.12</start>
    <end>00:52:47.24</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: What was that?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:52:47.25</start>
    <end>00:53:00.28</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Oh, I guess they don’t have it anymore. For like two or three years running they had an exotic dance night down there. And like, people would do crazy things. Some people would actually do like, dance-dancey. Do people still dress in costumes?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:53:00.29</start>
    <end>00:53:01.28</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Yes.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:53:01.29</start>
    <end>00:53:05.13</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: OK. So the gorilla who… oh, shoot, what’s his name?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:53:05.14</start>
    <end>00:53:06.03</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I don’t know.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:53:06.04</start>
    <end>00:53:54.19</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: He was a jerk. But he got up there in the gorilla suit to 'Pour Some Sugar On Me' and like, writhed around in the gorilla suit and then pulled out a five pound bag of sugar, dumped it all over himself and rolled around in it, which was awesome objectively but turns out that somebody else had just done an act with water, so it took like three weeks to clean up Bob’s. It was a mess, everyone was so mad. But, there was that. Oh, and Elizabeth Perrill did this- she would just, walked out and some normal song was playing and she like, undid all of her clothes, folded them quietly and then re-put them all back on and just walked offstage. That was pretty amazing. Oh, she had a baby recently, too.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:53:54.20</start>
    <end>00:53:55.18</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Oh really?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:53:55.19</start>
    <end>00:53:59.07</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Yeah, she’s out in... North Carolina. She’s in Greensboro.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:53:59.08</start>
    <end>00:54:00.26</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: There’s so many people in North Carolina.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:54:00.27</start>
    <end>00:54:30.26</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: I know, that’s where, it’s like a theater thing. She was at IU, too. But I remember all of that. I remember being in Bob’s early and Jennifer Hudson-Healy and someone else, whose name I can’t remember now, came iwith cowboy hats but no shirts on and everyone was kinda like, “Hm,” and kinda went about their business. So I would- I would think that, like that was a big thing. People were just, like you just trained yourself not to be surprised or shocked at anything.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:54:30.27</start>
    <end>00:54:34.23</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: The swim team, the night that they all shaved for the…</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:54:34.24</start>
    <end>00:54:36.06</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And then they streaked?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:54:36.07</start>
    <end>00:54:38.00</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Every year they’d streak the whole campus.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:54:38.01</start>
    <end>00:54:48.15</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Were you with me in Bob’s that night when we were all for, they were doing some sort of concerts, we were all laying on the floor? Everyone's just like lounging on the floor in Bob’s. Swim team comes in. They have to jump over everybody.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:54:48.16</start>
    <end>00:54:49.14</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs:  Oh, no.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:54:49.15</start>
    <end>00:55:16.22</end>
    <transcript>That’s a view, let me tell you. Like, “Oh, this is so, no, oh this is terrible! ...Did you finish your part of the project?” Yeah I just remember that, I think, these sort of collective experiences with the people who are doing the crazy things and experimenting and y’know, wearing the costumes and doing all this stuff. I think that, that would definitely go in there. That was cool, I liked that stuff.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:55:16.23</start>
    <end>00:55:21.18</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Well I don’t have any more questions, do you have anything to add?</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:55:21.19</start>
    <end>00:55:54.21</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Now I’ll remember like 900 more things as soon as we walk out. But… I will say, like today was really fun and last night, I remember we all went to watch Titular Head last night and that was all, that should probably go in there too. But I just remember everyone hootin’ and hollerin’ at Titular Head, We did our class picture and even though it wasn’t everybody that was there, we’re missing like big chunks of people, people were having such a fun time. Like, yelling at people coming in late and I was just, I really, I’m such a damn sap, but we were all like, “We’re like a family!” I think that still holds.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:55:54.22</start>
    <end>00:56:05.10</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Well yeah, I don’t know. I always, whenever I see the group of friends that I had at Grinnell I’m always amazed that…</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:56:05.11</start>
    <end>00:56:06.14</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: It doesn’t ever feel like time’s passed.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:56:06.15</start>
    <end>00:56:08.16</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah. It feels like we basically just left off. We still know each other.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:56:08.17</start>
    <end>00:56:11.29</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Yeah, I haven’t seen you in two years.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:56:12.00</start>
    <end>00:56:13.22</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah, I know, before that it was like..</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:56:13.23</start>
    <end>00:56:14.29</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Five years or so.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:56:15.00</start>
    <end>00:56:18.15</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Five or six or something like that.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:56:18.16</start>
    <end>00:56:20.01</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: No… yeah, whoa.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:56:20.02</start>
    <end>00:56:27.15</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: No. 2006 I was at your house. It was James that I hadn’t seen since graduation.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:56:27.16</start>
    <end>00:56:32.24</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Oh, that’s right, ‘cause you had to come to visit on your epic trip.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:56:32.25</start>
    <end>00:56:37.02</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: No, before that. Right after the whole end-of-the Mike thing.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:56:37.03</start>
    <end>00:56:39.08</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Right right, that's what I meant, when you were driving.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:56:39.09</start>
    <end>00:56:47.12</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: But basically, the whole point being that every time- we can go for very long periods of time without being in contact.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:56:47.13</start>
    <end>00:57:12.13</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And it’s as if no time has passed. It’s been really trippy the last couple, ‘cause you’re like, “Oh hey you,” after you do your initial hug and how are things and then you just kinda like stand there blankly because it’s totally normal, and so you realize, “Oh, I haven’t seen you in six years, I’m not gonna see you again for another five or six years, we can probably talk more about things of consequence.” But I don’t feel like it, I just wanna talk about 'how good that person’s hair looks now,'... 'did you see over there?'</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:57:12.14</start>
    <end>00:57:17.07</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: I think it’s gonna be fine because it’s six years, we have this conversation right where we left off.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:57:17.08</start>
    <end>00:57:29.23</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: It’ll be the same damn thing. In that case, yeah, it doesn’t feel like- I mean, it feels like time has passed, but not in any sort of significant way.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:57:29.24</start>
    <end>00:57:31.01</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Doesn’t feel like ten years.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:57:31.02</start>
    <end>00:57:34.22</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Plus none of us have aged as dramatically as I thought we would, so good job.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:57:34.23</start>
    <end>00:57:37.10</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: None of us look older than we did ten years ago.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:57:37.11</start>
    <end>00:57:39.12</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: We did come of age in the time of sunscreen, though.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:57:39.13</start>
    <end>00:57:40.15</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Yeah, thank god.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:57:40.16</start>
    <end>00:57:45.20</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: And really good hair dye, so there you go.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:57:45.21</start>
    <end>00:57:51.17</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: So yeah, I think... We good? Oh we did a thing, yay!</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:57:51.18</start>
    <end>00:57:53.09</end>
    <transcript>Heather Riggs: Well thanks so much!</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:57:53.10</start>
    <end>00:57:53.28</end>
    <transcript>Allison Foley: Thank you.</transcript>
  </cue>
  <cue>
    <speaker/>
    <start>00:57:53.29</start>
    <end>00:57:54.13</end>
    <transcript>Tyler Bradbury: Thank you.</transcript>
  </cue>
</cues>
